Guide to the Robert L. Patten academic papers, 1963-2015 MS 410
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series I: General Academic Files, 1963-2005, Includes files relating to Robert L. Patten's involvement in professional associations and committees (Rice University and others), correspondence, lectures, early writings, student advising and other professional and academic activities.
  - Dickens Quarterly, regarding Bill Axton, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Visual Culture position search, 2001 January (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Houston Seminar, 2001 April (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Victorian Marriage Plot, mini-conference, 2001 May (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Dickens Society, 2001 Fall (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - MLA, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Victorian Geographics, 2001-2002 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Teaching Awards, Continuting Studies, 2001-2002 (Box 6)
  - Dickens Project, Winter conference, 2001-2002 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Renaissance literature candidates, 2002 January (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Joel Bratten, correspondence, 2002 January - February (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - RUSP, 2002 January - February (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Fathom course, 2002 February - June (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - RUSP, Spring 2002 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - 9/11 memorial, 2002 May-September (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - New York Public Library, 2002 June (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Free Library of Philadelphia, Dickens exhibition, 2002 June - August (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - John Glavin visit, 2002 September - December (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - 19th Century Geographies, contract, 2002 October (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Free Library of Philadelphia, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - MLA, Dickens Panel, 2002 November - 2003 February (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Gregory Kaplan course, 2002-2003 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Philip Gossett, 2002-2003 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Dickens Winter conference, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Dave Kopay visit, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - New CELJ award, 2003-2004 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Oxford Dictionary of National Biography, 2001 April - May (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Lew Eatherton talk, "NetBook Agreement," 2004 December 10 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - John Glavin visit, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Years work in Victorian Studies, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Oxford Encyclopedia of British Literature, "Nineteenth Century Book Illustration," 2004-2005 (Box 6, Folder 44-45)
  - Studies in the Novel, review, 2004-2005 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Society of Rice University Women, "Happy Birthday Charles Dickens," 2005 February 7 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Series II: Teaching Files, 1969-2004
  - English 355a: Early Victorian Literarture, 1969 Fall (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - English 566: Victorian Seminar, 1969 Fall (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - English 340b: 19th Century Novel, 1970 Spring (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - English Honors Seminars, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - English 565a: The Long Victorian Poem, 1970 Fall (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - English 355a: Early Victorian Literature, 1970 Fall (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - English 340b: The Victorian Novel, 1971 Spring (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - English 355b: The Later Victorian Period, 1971 Spring (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - English 515b: Victorian Pro-Seminar, 1971 Spring (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - English 355a: Early Victorian Literature, 1971 Fall (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - English Honors Seminar, 1971 Fall (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - English 340b: The Victorian Novel, 1972 Spring (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - English 355b: Middle and Late Victorians, 1972 Spring (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - English 100a: Critical Reading and Writing, 1973 Fall (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - English 566a: Dickens Graduate Seminar, 1973 Fall (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - English 250b: Masters of English Literature, 1974 Spring (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - English 340b: 1974 Spring (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - English 454b: Balzac and Dickens, 1974 Spring (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - English 101a: Critical Reading and Writing, 1974 Fall (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - English 515a: Victorian Pro-Seminar, 1974 Fall (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - English 252b: Masters of English Literature, 1975 Spring (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - English 342b: The English Novel in the 19th Century, 1975 Spring (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - English 101a: Freshman Seminar, 1975 Fall (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - English 565a: The Long Victorian Poem, 1975 Fall (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - English 581a: Directed Reading in the English 18th Century Novel, 1975 Fall (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - English 306b: Studies in a Major Writer - Charles Dickens, 1976 Spring (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - English 342b: English Novel in the 19th Century, 1976 Spring (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - English 515b: Victorian Pro-Seminar, 1977 Spring (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - English 342b: English Novel in 19th Century, 1977 Spring (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - English - Intrusive Narrator in Victorian Fiction, circa 1977 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - English, "Evolution and Entropy in 19th Century Literature," circa 1978 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - English 503: Introduction to Graduate Study, 1978 Fall (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - English 566a: Charles Dickens in Context, 1978 Fall (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - English 342b: English Novel in the 19th Century, 1979 Spring (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - English 361a: 18th Century British Fiction, 1979 Fall (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - English 362b: 19th Century British Fiction, 1980 Spring (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - English 562b: 19th Century British Fiction, 1980 Spring (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - English 622b: Directed Reading in 18th Century British Fiction, 1980 Spring (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - English 403a: Studies in a Major British Author - Charles Dickens, 1982 Fall (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - English 357b: Victorian Literature, 1983 Spring (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Continuing Studies, "Oliver with a Twist," 1983 Spring (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - English 362a: 19th Century British Fiction, 1983 Fall (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - English 562a: 19th Century Novel, 1983 Fall (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - English 252b: Major British Writers, 1984 Spring (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - English 401b: Crime and Punishment in Victorian England, 1984 Spring (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - English 357: Victorian Literature, 1984 Fall (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - English 357: British Literature of the Victorian Period, 1984 Fall (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - English 102: Critical Reading and Writing/Poetry, 1985 Spring (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - English 562: 19th Century British Fiction, 1985 Spring (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - English 362: 19th Century British Fiction, 1985 Spring (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - English 369: The Novel, Cervantes to 1900, 1985 Fall (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - English 404: Charles Dickens, 1985 Fall (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - English 252b: Major British Writers - 1800 to Present, 1986 Spring (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - English 362: 19th Century British Fiction, 1986 Spring (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - English 562: 19th Century British Fiction, 1986 Spring (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - English 357: British Literature of the Victorian Period, 1986 Fall (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - English 369: The Novel - Cervantes to 1900, 1986 Fall (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - English 557: British Literature of the Victorian Period, 1986 Fall (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - English 252: Major British Writers - 1800 to present, 1987 Spring (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - English 362: 19th Century British Fiction, 1987 Spring (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - English 562: 19th Century British Fiction, 1987 Spring (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - English 369: The Novel - Cervantes to 1900, 1989 Fall (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - English 511: The Long Victorian Poem, 1989 Fall (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - English 403: Studies in Major British Authors - Dickens, 1990 Fall (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - English 252: Major British Writers, 1800 - Present, 1990 Spring (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - English 252: Major British Writers, 1800 to Present, 1981 Spring (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - English 515: Pedagogy class materials, 1991 Fall (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - English 501: Directed Reading, 1991 Fall (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - English 622: Directed Reading, 1992 Spring (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - English 362: Nineteenth-Century British Fiction, class materials, 1992 Fall (Box 7, Folder 72)
  - English 252.1: Major British Writers, 1800 - Present, class materials, 1993 Spring (Box 7, Folder 73)
  - English 252.2: Major British Writers, 1800-Present, class materials, 1993 Spring (Box 7, Folder 74)
  - Continuing Studies, "What Makes Great Fiction Great," 1993 Spring (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Continuing Studies, "Art Politics: The Cruikshank Mix," 1993 March (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Continuing Studies: Master Teachers Course, 1993 April (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - English 517: Textual Embodiments in 19th Century Fiction, class materials, 1994 Spring (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - English 363: 19th Century British Fiction, 1995 Spring (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Continuing Studies, "From Mayhem to Murder: Mystery Fiction at Its Best," 1995 Spring (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - English 211.2: Major British Writers, 1800 - Present, 1997 Spring (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - English 491: Studies in Major British Authors - Dickens, 1997 Fall (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - HONS 470, 1997 Fall (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - English 543: Victorian Poetry and Prose, 1998 Spring (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - English 511: Pedagogy, class materials, 1998 Spring (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - English 603: Pedagogy, class materials, 1998 Fall (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - English 211, Major British Writers, 1800-Present, 1999 Spring (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - English 437: History of the Book in 19th Century Britain, 1999 Fall (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - English 494: Autobiographies, Letters, and Journals: A Student Led Seminar, 2000 Spring (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - English 211: Major British Writers, 1800 - Present, 2000 Spring (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - English 491: Studies in Major British Authors - Dickens, 2000 Fall (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Continuing Studies, "Re-Imagining Copyright: The Victorian Dilemma," 2000 November (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - English 341/622: Victorian Literature, Excluding Fiction, 2001 Spring (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Continuing Studies, "Victoria and the Victorians," 2001 Fall (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Continuing Studies, "Introduction to the English Country House," 2003 March (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - English 490.1: Major British Authors - Charles Dickens and the Birth of the Industrial Strength Author, 2003 Fall (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - English 605, Caroline Levander class, 2003 Fall (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - English 543: Victorian Poetry and Prose, 2004 Spring (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Caroline Levander, Writing Workshop and Frances Ferguson visit, 2004 Fall (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Series III: Palgrave Advances in Charles Dickens Studies, 2000-2006, Correspondence, proofs, contracts and other materials relating to the publication of Palgrave Advances in Charles Dickens Studies, 2006, edited by Robert L. Patten and published by Palgrave Macmillan.
  - John Bowen, Eleanor Birne, 2000-2001 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Eleanor Birne, 2000-2002 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Palgrave/MacMillan, general correspondence, 2000-2005 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - John Bowen, 2001-2003 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Palgrave, sytle protocols, 2002, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Rosemarie Bodenheimer, 2002-2005 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Joseph Childers, 2002-2005 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Helena Michie, 2002-2005 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Robert L. Patten, 2002-2005 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - John Sutherland, 2002-2005 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - David Vincent, 2002-2005 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Palgrave, contracts, contacts, 2002-2006 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Carolyn Deaver, 2002-2006 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Emily Rosser, Paula Kennedy, 2002-2006 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Steven Connor, 2003-2004 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Palgrave, chapter material, 2003-2004 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Catherine M. Robson, 2003-2005 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Hilary M. Schor, 2003-2005 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Catherine Waters, 2003-2005 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - John Bowen, 2003-2006 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Palgrave, tracking chart, 2004-2005 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - John Bowen, essay, correspondence, 2004-2005 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Paula Kennedy, 2004-2006 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Malcolm Andrews, 2004-2006 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Palgrave, Introduction, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Essay, "Performing Character," Malcolm Andrews, [2005] (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Essay, "Dickens and the Writing of a Life," Rosemarie Bodenheimer, [2005] (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Essay, "Dickens and the Force of Writing," John Bowen, [2005] (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Essay, "Psychoanalyzing Dickens," Carolyn Deaver, [2005] (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Essay, "From Blood to Law: The Embarrassments of Family in Dickens," Helena Michie, [2005] (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Essay, "Publishing in Parts," Robert L. Patten, [2005] (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Robert L. Patten, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Essay, "Historicizing Dickens," Catherine Robson, [2005] (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Essay, "Dickens and Plot," Hilary Schor, [2005] (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Essay, "Visualizing Dickens," John Sutherland, [2005] (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Essay, "Politicized Dickens: The Journalism of the 1850s," Joseph W. Childers, [2005] (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Essay, "Dickens Reading Public," David Vincent, [2005] (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Essay, "Reforming Culture," Catherine Waters, [2005] (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Palgrace Advances in Charles Dickens Studies, proof, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Proof, front matter - Chapter 9, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Chapter 10 - Acknowledgments, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Palgrave, Index, [2005] (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Bibliography, [2005] (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Literature Online, search results, "Abell," 2005 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Helene Craine, Oliver Howard, 2005-2006 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Reviews, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 37)
- Series IV: Swarthmore College, 1971-1982
  - Recruiting, 1971-1975 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Alumni Council, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Alumni Council, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Committee on course/honors curriculum, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Admissions, 1977-1980 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Extern Program, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Alumni Council/Association, 1978-1979 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Recruiting, 1982-1985 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Series V: Personal, other administrative papers, 1988-1993
  - Robert L. Patten, administrative correspondence, biographical materials, 1988-1997 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Theresa Munisteri, 2003-2006 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Professor Jane Chance, correpondence, memoranda, clippings, 1987-1993 (Box 11, Folder 4-8)
- Series VI: Addenda
  - Subseries A: Correspondence
    - A-Bewley, Susan (Box 12)
    - Beverly Hills High School - Carmichael, Virginia (Box 13)
    - Carrell, Betty - Conrad, Peter (Box 14)
    - Considine, Ellen - Davidson, Jane (Box 15)
    - Davies, Donna - Evans, Linda (Box 16)
    - F - Finkelstein, David (Box 17)
    - Finkelstein, David - Fletcher, Robert (Box 18)
    - Flint, Kate - Fulbright (Box 19)
    - Fultz, Lucie - Gardner, Laura (Box 20)
    - Gardner, Laura - Gates, Barbara (Box 21)
    - Gaull, Marilyn - Gould, Marilyn (Box 22)
    - Gould, Marty - Grossman, Jonathan (Box 23)
    - Guest, Bill - Harmless, Bill (Box 24)
    - Harper, Jessica - Hecht, J. Jean (Box 25)
    - Hedley, Jane - Hewitt, Janice L. (Box 26)
    - Hicks, Marion - Hochstettler, Tom (Box 27)
    - Hodges, Laura - Howard, Richard (Box 28)
    - Howe, Harlan George III - Hyman, Harold and Bill (Box 29)
    - I - Jewitt, Lucy (Box 30)
    - Jewitt, William - Jordan, John (Box 31)
    - Jordan, John - Kermode Frank (Box 32)
    - Kermode, Lloyd - Kung, Hans (Box 33)
    - Kunzle, David - Lazo, Andrew (Box 34)
    - Leary, Patrick - Lew, Judy (Box 35)
    - Lewis, Karen - Logan, Thad and Jill (Box 36)
    - Long, Elizabeth - Markey, Sister Joan (Box 37)
    - Marriott, John - McCleery, Alistair (Box 38)
    - McDonald, Pat - Meeuwis, Michael (Box 39)
    - Meisel, Martin - Miner, Heather (Box 40)
    - Minter, David and Caroline - Morrison, Kevin (Box 41)
    - Munich, Adrienne - Needleman, Deborah (Box 42)
    - Neely, Eugene - Oberhelman, David (Box 43)
    - Oberhelman, David - Page, Norman (Box 44)
    - Pappakonstantinou, Joanna - Partlow, Robert (Box 45)
    - Partlow, Robert - Perlitz, Charles (Box 46)
    - Pettitt, Clare - Porterfield, Todd (Box 47)
    - Poston, Lawrence III - Ray, Gordon (Box 48)
    - Ray, Laura Krugman - Royal Shakespeare Co. (Box 49)
    - Ruff, Sue and Chuck - Salvaggio, Ruth (Box 50)
    - Sborovy, Katherine - Schor, Hilary (Box 51)
    - Schor, Hilary - Shesgreen Sean (Box 52)
    - Shillingsburg, Peter - Slater, Michael (Box 53)
    - Slattery, Molly - Snodgrass, Charles (Box 54)
    - Snow, Ed - Stern, Rebecca (Box 55)
    - Stern, Rebecca - Symmes, Marilyn (Box 56)
    - Szalkowski, Charles - Thompson, Gary (Box 57)
    - Thockmorton, Joanna - Varese, John Michael (Box 58)
    - Van Helden, Albert - Welch, Diana (Box 59)
    - Wellner, Julia - Winship, Michael (Box 60)
    - Winship, Michael - Worthington, Geroge Marshall (Box 61)
    - Wright, Edward N. - Zentner, Rene D. (Box 62)
  - Subseries B: Courses
    - Eng. 250b (Jim Cagle's notes), 1970 (Box 62, Folder 15)
    - Eng. 401b (folder 1/2), 1984 (Box 62, Folder 16)
    - Eng. 401b (folder 1/2), 1984 (Box 62, Folder 17)
    - Brown College - Introduction to Gay/Lesbian Studies, 1994/1995 (Box 62, Folder 18)
    - Eng. 537 (folder 1/3), Fall 2004 (Box 62, Folder 19)
    - Eng. 537 (folder 2/3), Fall 2004 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Eng. 537 (folder 2/3), Fall 2004 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Eng. 403, undated (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Eng. 342 (folder 1/2), Spring 2005 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Eng. 342 (folder 2/2), Spring 2005 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Eng. 537 (folder 1/2), Spring 2006 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Eng. 537 (folder 2/2), Spring 2006 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Eng. 541 (folder 1/2), Spring 2007 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Eng. 541 (folder 2/2), Spring 2007 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Eng. 175, 2007/2008 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Eng. 605, Fall 2007 (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Eng. 600 - revised, Fall 2008 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Eng. 605 - review, 2008 (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - Eng. 510 - II, 2008 (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - Eng. 605 (folder 1/2), 2008/2009 (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - Eng. 605 (folder 2/2), 2008/2009 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Eng. 541, Spring 2009 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Victorian Studies Seminars, Fall 2010 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Eng. 600, 2007-2009 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - On Writing Papers and Speaking and Jokes, undated (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Grade book, 1964-1965 (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Grade book, 1966-1968 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Grade book, 1969-1971 (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - Grade book, 1972 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Grade book, 1973-1977 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Grade book, 1978-1985 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Grade book, 1986-2000 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Grade book, 200-2007 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Subseries C: Student Papers
    - Brind, Frederica Wolf, March 1972 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Celikkol, Ayse, May 2002 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Cleere, Eileen, May 1996 (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - Crosthwait, Ginny (folder 1/2), 2002 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Crosthwait, Ginny (folder 2/2), 2002 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Crutchfield, Lilian, 2008 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Dayton, Anne (folder 1/3) (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Dayton, Anne (folder 2/3) (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Dayton, Anne (folder 3/3) (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Demirhan, Basak (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Francis, Pamela, 2006-2008 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Frolic, Andrea N., 2003-2005 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Hanssen, Susan E., May 2002 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Hasell, Duncan (folder 1/2) (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Hasell, Duncan (folder 1/2) (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Hariprasad, Jaya, December 1999 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Heath, Kay Helen (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Klein, Andy, 2008-2009 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Koh, Eun-Young, 2005-2008 (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - Lourence, Ben, 2007-2009 (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - Marler-Kennedy, Kara (folder 1/2), 2010 (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - Marler-Kennedy, Kara (folder 2/2), 2010 (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - Moore, Robert George, September 1991 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Morrison, Kevin, 2004-2009 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - Robey, Molly, undated (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - Roberts, Bettie (folder 1/2), 1983-1998 (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - Roberts, Bettie (folder 2/2), 1983-1998 (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - Vogel, Brian, January 2009 (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - Womack, Elizabeth Coggin, undated (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - Student Papers Addenda
      - Jackson, Jeffrey E. (Box 71a, Folder 1-7)
  - Subseries D: Rice-Related
    - AAUP/Copyright (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Academic Climate Survey, 2004 (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Admissions (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Advisory Committee (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - Affirmative Action (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - Alumni Association (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - Alumni College, 2005 (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - Alumni College, March 2006 (Box 72, Folder 8)
    - Americas Project (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - Americas Project correspondence (Box 72, Folder 10)
    - Amorous Relationship Policy (Box 72, Folder 11)
    - ARA, 2011 (Box 72, Folder 12)
    - Art Historian search, 200-2001 (Box 72, Folder 13)
    - Art History Chair, 1998-1999 (Box 72, Folder 14)
    - Association of Rice Alumni (Box 72, Folder 15)
    - Athletics, 2002-2003 (Box 72, Folder 16)
    - Baker College (Box 72, Folder 17)
    - Baker Institute (Box 72, Folder 18)
    - Banned Book Week (Box 72, Folder 19)
    - Benefits/pay (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Brown College (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Brown Foundation (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Censorship (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Centennial Campaign (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - Commencement packets and programs (folder 1/2) (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Commencement packets and programs (folder 2/2) (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - Committee on Teaching, 2007-2008 (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - Courses, 2009-2010 (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - Dean of Humanities (Box 73, Folder 10)
    - English 100 - Distribution, 2006-2007 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - English Department, 2001-2006 (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - English Department, 2007- (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - English Department - Library business (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - English Department - Reference folder, 2004-2006 (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - English Department retreat, April 23, 2009 (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - English Department Speakers Committee, 2005-2006 (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - Executive Committee, 2006-2008 (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - External Review, 2000 (Box 74, Folder 9)
    - Faculty announcements (Box 74, Folder 10)
    - Faculty Council (folder 1/2), 1998-1999 (Box 74, Folder 11)
    - Faculty Council (folder 2/2), 2008-2009 (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - Faculty Feminist Reading Group (folder 1/2), 1990-1992 (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - Faculty Feminist Reading Group (folder 2/2), 1990-1992 (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - Faculty Senate, 2005 (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - Fondren Library (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - Friends of Fondren Library - Shakepeare's First Folio correspondence, 2007 (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - Friends of Fondren - Truxillo, 2003 (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - GLBT - Council on Diversity (folder 1/2) (Box 75, Folder 8)
    - GLBT - Council on Diversity (folder 2/2) (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - GLBT/Pride, 1996-1998 (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - Grad News - Susan Lurie, 2004 (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - Graduate Admissions, 2008-2009 (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - Graduate Alumni Committee, 2001-2009 (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - Graduate Apartments/The Watcher, 1998-2003 (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - Graduate Committee, 1998-1999 (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - Graduate Committee, 2006 (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Graduate Committee, 2008-2009 (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - Graduate Committee, 2010-2011 (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - Graduate Comittee - course schedules (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - Graduate Orientation programs, 2005-2008 (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - Graduate Research Grants/Funding, 2006-2007 (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - GSA, Spring 2007-Summer 2008 (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - GSA, Fall 2008-Winter 2010 (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - GSA Alcohol Policies (folder 1/2) (Box 78, Folder 2)